CONTACT

akshaysalokhe@hotmail.com

+91 9850454145

Pune, Maharashtra, India

TECHINICAL SKILLS

Angular 2+ to 15

ReactJS

Java J2EE, Servlet, SpringBoot

NodeJS

Core PHP, Laravel, Symphony

MySQL / PostgreSQL

MongoDB

GIT, AWS

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES

Requirement Analysis

Agile methodology

Performance Optimization

PERSONAL SKILLS

High level of persuasiveness

Good Managerial Skills

Good Inter-personal Skills

AWARDS

Rising Star Award 2022-06-06 Calsoft

EDUCATION

Master's in Computer Application (MCA) Jul 2013 - May 2016 Shivaji University

Bachelor's in Computer Application (BCA) Jul 2010 - May 2013 Shivaji University

AKSHAY SALOKHE

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

To work with leading company to contribute to organization's growth and goal, as well as to attain my personal goal

SUMMARY

Worked as Senior Software Developer with upto 8 years of experience in the software engineering industry. Highly skilled with proven records of success in leading successful development projects and providing technical guidance to team members. Accomplished with expertise in agile development, system design, and project management.

EXPERIENCE

EXFO India Pvt. Ltd..Pune

Nov 2023 - Present

Senior Software Developer

Calsoft Pvt. Ltd., Bavdhan, Pune

Oct 2021 - Oct 2023

Sr. Principal Development Engineer

Aloha Technology, Baner, Pune

Aug 2016 - Sep 2021

Sr. Software Developer

PROJECTS

Fiber Monitoring & Graphical Information System, Global (3 Years)

- Type: Web Application (Angular 14/15, NodeJS, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL)
- Description: FMS is for monitoring optical fibers, Topology view & map view for showing cables & sites, also used web-sockets for showing live data
- Responsibilities: Client Communication, Team Management, Requirement Analysis, Creating REST API's (Java Spring Boot), Live Data using websockets

Orchestrator Portal for 5G Technology, Japan (1.5 Year)

- Type: Web Application (Angular 12, Material CS, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL)
- **Description**: It is an admin portal for Orchestrator user to manage the network services, network functions & hardware devices for 5G technology
- **Responsibilities**: Client Communication, Requirement Analysis, designing (Angular 12, Material CS), Creating REST API's (Java Spring Boot)

Fleet Solutions, USA (2 Years)

- Type: Web Application (AngularJS & 2+, PHP Zend Framework, MySQL)
- **Description**: Provides service like emergency road service, towing, accident management, scheduled & preventive maintenance.
- **Responsibilities**: Client Communication, Requirement Analysis, designing, Coding, Created DB object & Stored Procedures, Report Development

Smart Covid Band, USA (1 Year)

- Type: Web Application (Angular 9, Node JS, Mongo DB
- **Description**: It is a web admin portal to shows all information related to all smart band users, it shows temperature, health rating
- Responsibilities: Client Communication, Requirement Analysis, designing, Creating REST API's for web, android & iOS apps, Creating Mongo Collections